Finn Huynh

admin@finnhuynh.me|North York, ON M3A 2Y7| (647) 819-0382

Finn Huynh | In Finn Huynh | 6 finnhuynh.me

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

• B.S. in Computer Science from Ryerson University. Maintained 4.03/4.33 CGPA.

Had experience with Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, React.js, Node.js, RESTful API, and JSON.

Understood software development lifecycle as well as Data Structures and Algorithms.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Development: JavaScript • HTML5 • CSS3 • Python • Java

Tools: Office 365: Word, PowerPoint • Git • GitHub • Heroku • Postman Framework: React.js • Node.js • Express.js • Bootstrap • Styled components

Database: MongoDB • Excel

Other: Leadership • Critical Thinking • Collaborative • Creative • Agile Project Management • English/Vietnamese

EDUCATION

Ryerson University

2019 – 2023 (expected graduate)

Toronto, ON, Canada

BSc Computer Science, Minor Psychology - 4.03/4.33 CGPA

• Selected for the 2019-2020 Dean's List.

Courses: Python OPP | Java OPP | Data Algorithms | Web System Development | Software Engineering

PROJECTS

Web Development - MovieCrunchers | HTML • CSS • JavaScript • PHP

Oct 2020 - Nov 2020

Site

- Implemented a movie review website and platform for user interaction from concept through completion, optimized all cross-browser, and multi-platform compatibility.
- Assessed UX, UI designs for technical feasibility, and increased team productivity by 30-40%.
- Collaborated with three other group team members to implement new features and reduce project duration by 33%.

React.js Development - Searchable movie App | JavaScript • Bootstrap • React.js

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020

Site

- Accomplished pagination, sorting, searching, authentication, authorization, and routing.
- Created a variety of reusable components and improved efficiency in other projects by 20-30%.
- Reduced code for validating form by 70-80% and increased security by applying Joi and jwt-decode libraries.

App Development - Student Registry | Java

Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

GitHub

- Constructed an object-oriented Ryerson student registry to maintain a list of registered students and a list of active courses that are currently running.
- Applied inheritance and polymorphism concepts to form subclasses for credit courses and active courses.
- Implemented comparators to filter students by ID, names, and courses taken.

EXPERIENCE

SUPERVISOR - THE BURGER'S PRIEST

Nov 2019 - Present

Downtown Toronto, ON

- Evaluated situations and prioritize activities when short-staffed.
- Delegated each employee to appropriate roles based on their strengths and weaknesses.
- Lessened wait time for customers and boosted their satisfaction by 30%.
- Decreased labor costs by undertaking the work of 2 people.
- Cross-trained and coordinated scheduling with team members to ensure seamless services.

CO-FOUNDER - LTES - LET'S FLY HIGH

Jun 2016 - Jun 2019

Vietnam

Site

- Organized Summer Camp for the ages from 14 to 17 locally.
- Extended page interaction through advertising plans by more than 1000% in the time period.
- Decided to shorten or prolong the duration of the camp based on weather or unexpected situations by creating more challenges or cutting unnecessary details.
- Recruited Organization Committee annually so that the Summer Camp will occur in the year to come.